By the way
What's with that outfit?
He's all dressed up
Who is he trying
to impress?
Here, Hyeon-wu
The side
without walnuts
D***, that's gross
Get that away
from me
That looks yummy, Il-tak
I already ate
the walnut part
It's okay, I don't care
Thanks for the food!
Hey, I'm sorry
You really
like these, huh?
You can have all of them
I said I don't
like walnuts, you idiot
I'm eating
Il-tak's walnut cookie
D*** it, d*** it
Settle down
I'll call out your names
-for room assignments
-Yes
Understood?
Yes!
And if you guys
brought alcohol…
Please let me be
in Hyeon-wu's room
Please don't let me be
in Hyeong-ju's room
Got it?
Room 301
Lee Seong-ju
Kim Do-jun, Kim Ki-tae
Room 302, Nam Jun-wu
Jeong Seong-jo
My room sucks
Plus
both of them
are in different rooms
One of you
except Hong Il-tak
Move to Room 307
Kim Hyeong-ju?
Why is he being
such a pain even here?
Hey, is Hong Il-tak here?
Huh? Lee Hyeon-wu too?
My room has an open spot